## Vignesh S Bandi

Legal Counsel/ Associate at Equis Funds Group

## Summary

Australian-registered lawyer admitted as a solicitor to the Supreme Court of Queensland and entered on the High Court of Australia Register of Practitioners.

Prior to joining Equis Funds Group, spent 3+ years as a litigation and dispute resolution lawyer with international US law firm, K&L Gates.

## Experience

#### Associate at Japan Solar (an Equis Funds Group invested platform)

July 2016 - Present (9 months)

#### Legal Counsel at Equis Funds Group

March 2016 - Present (1 year 1 month)

#### Lawyer (Commercial Litigation) at K&L Gates

February 2013 - March 2016 (3 years 2 months)

#### Graduate Lawyer (Disputes and Litigation/ Property and Projects) at DibbsBarker

February 2012 - February 2013 (1 year 1 month)

#### Graduate Corporate Solicitor (Secondment) at Bank of Queensland

May 2012 - June 2012 (2 months)

#### Research Clerk (Commerical/Insurance) at DibbsBarker

September 2010 - February 2012 (1 year 6 months)

#### Legal Intern at Ravindran Associates

January 2010 - March 2010 (3 months)

#### Education

#### **Chartered Institute of Arbitrators**

Introduction to International Arbitration - Introductory Certificate, 2015 - 2015

#### The College of Law

Graduate Diploma of Legal Practice, Law, 2012 - 2012

#### The University of Queensland

Bachelor of Laws (LLB), Law, 2006 - 2011

### The University of Queensland

Bachelor of Science (BSc), Biomedical Sciences, General, 2006 - 2011

## Skills & Expertise

**Commercial Litigation** 

**Bankruptcy** 

Construction

**Dispute Resolution** 

**Commercial Real Estate** 

**Insurance** 

**Dispute** 

**Financial Services** 

**Due Diligence** 

**Insurance Law** 

**Legal Advice** 

Leases

**Legal Research** 

**Legal Writing** 

**Intellectual Property** 

Litigation

**Personal Injury** 

Mediation

**Real Estate Transactions** 

**Managed Funds** 

**Private Equity** 

# Vignesh S Bandi

Legal Counsel/ Associate at Equis Funds Group



Contact Vignesh S on LinkedIn